pixiemarket.com 2019-02-02

# Privacy Statement

Pixie Market PRIVACY STATEMENT

This Privacy Policy describes how your personal information is collected, used and shared when you visit or make a purchase at pixiemarket.com

**Section 1 – What do we do with your information?**

When you purchase something from Pixie Market, as part of the buying and selling process, we collect the personal information you give us such as your name, address and email address. When you browse our store, we also automatically receive your computer’s internet protocol (IP) , web browser, time zone and some of the cookies that are installed in your device.   We collect Device information using cookies. Cookies are data files that are placed on your computer and include an anonymous unique identifier. To disable the cookies in you device or to learn more about cookies, please visit : http://www.allaboutcookies.org

We use your Device information to help us screen for potential risk and fraud (your IP address) and to improve and optimize our Site (by using analytics to assess the success of our marketing and advertising campaigns)

Email marketing (if applicable): With your permission, we may send you emails about our store, new products and other updates.

**Section 2 – Consent**

How do you get my consent?   
When you provide us with personal information to complete a transaction, verify your credit card, place an order, arrange for a delivery or return a purchase, add your name to the waitlist, we imply that you consent to our collecting it and using it for that specific reason only. 

If we ask for your personal information for a secondary reason, like marketing, we will either ask you directly for your expressed consent, or provide you with an opportunity to say no.

How do I withdraw my consent?   
If after you opt-in, you change your mind, you may withdraw your consent for us to contact you, for the continued collection, use or disclosure of your information, at anytime, by notifying us at the contact information below.

**Section 3 – Disclosure**

We share your information with Google analytics to help us understand how our customers use the Site. You can read more about how google uses your personal data here: https://policies.google.com/privacy. You may also opt out of Google’s collection and processing of data generated by your use of the Services here: http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout.

We may disclose your personal information if we are required by law to do so or if you violate our Terms of Service.

**Section 4 – Data Retention**

Our store is hosted on Shopify Inc. They provide us with the online e-commerce platform that allows us to sell our products and services to you.   
Your data is stored through Shopify’s data storage, databases and the general Shopify application. They store your data on a secure server behind a firewall.  
We will maintain your Order Information for our records unless and until you ask us to delete this information.

Payment:   
If you choose a direct payment gateway to complete your purchase, then Shopify stores your credit card data. It is encrypted through the Payment Card Industry Data Security Standard (PCI-DSS). Your purchase transaction data is stored only as long as is necessary to complete your purchase transaction. After that is complete, your purchase transaction information is deleted.   
All direct payment gateways adhere to the standards set by PCI-DSS as managed by the PCI Security Standards Council, which is a joint effort of brands like Visa, MasterCard, American Express and Discover.   
PCI-DSS requirements help ensure the secure handling of credit card information by our store and its service providers.   
For more insight, you may also want to read Shopify’s Terms of Service (https://www.shopify.com/legal/terms) or Privacy Statement

**Section 5 - Third-party Services**

In general, the third-party providers used by us will only collect, use and disclose your information to the extent necessary to allow them to perform the services they provide to us.

However, certain third-party service providers, such as payment gateways and other payment transaction processors, have their own privacy policies in respect to the information we are required to provide to them for your purchase-related transactions.

For these providers, we recommend that you read their privacy policies so you can understand the manner in which your personal information will be handled by these providers.

In particular, remember that certain providers may be located in or have facilities that are located a different jurisdiction than either you or us. So if you elect to proceed with a transaction that involves the services of a third-party service provider, then your information may become subject to the laws of the jurisdiction(s) in which that service provider or its facilities are located.

As an example, if you are located in the EU and your transaction is processed by a payment gateway located in the United States, then your personal information used in completing that transaction may be subject to disclosure under United States legislation, including the Patriot Act.

Once you leave our store’s website or are redirected to a third-party website or application, you are no longer governed by this Privacy Policy or our website’s Terms of Service.

When you click on links on our store, they may direct you away from our site. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of other sites and encourage you to read their privacy statements.

**Section 6 - Security**

To protect your personal information, we take reasonable precautions and follow industry best practices to make sure it is not inappropriately lost, misused, accessed, disclosed, altered or destroyed.

If you provide us with your credit card information, the information is encrypted using secure socket layer technology (SSL) and stored with a AES-256 encryption. Although no method of transmission over the Internet or electronic storage is 100% secure, we follow all PCI-DSS requirements and implement additional generally accepted industry standards.

**Section 7 - Cookies**

Here is a list of cookies that we use. We’ve listed them here so you that you can choose if you want to opt-out of cookies or not.  
_session_id, unique token, sessional, Allows Shopify to store information about your session (referrer, landing page, etc).  
_shopify_visit, no data held, Persistent for 30 minutes from the last visit, Used by our website provider’s internal stats tracker to record the number of visits  
_shopify_uniq, no data held, expires midnight (relative to the visitor) of the next day, Counts the number of visits to a store by a single customer.  
cart, unique token, persistent for 2 weeks, Stores information about the contents of your cart.  
_secure_session_id, unique token, sessional  
storefront_digest, unique token, indefinite If the shop has a password, this is used to determine if the current visitor has access.

**Google Analytics:**  This cookie allows us to see information on user website activities including, but not limited to page views, source, and time spent on our website. The information is depersonalized and is displayed as numbers, meaning it cannot be tracked back to individuals. This will help to protect your privacy. Using Google Analytics we can see what content is popular on our website, and strive to give you more of the things you enjoy reading and watching.

**Google AdWords:**  Using Google AdWords code we are able to see which pages helped lead to sale. This allows us to make better use of our paid search budget.

**DoubleClick:**  We use remarketing codes to log when users view specific pages, allowing us to provide targeted advertising in the future.

**Section 8 - Age of Consent**

By using this site, you represent that you are at least the age of majority in your state or province of residence, or that you are the age of majority in your state or province of residence and you have given us your consent to allow any of your minor dependents to use this site.

**Section 9 - Changes to the Privacy Policy**

This Privacy Policy may change from time to time. You understand and agree that you will be deemed to have accepted the updated Privacy Policy if you use the Services after the updated Privacy Policy is posted on the Services.By continuing to visit and shop at Pixiemarket.com on or after May 25,2018, you acknowledge our updated privacy policy and terms and conditions.

If at any point you do not agree to any portion of the Privacy Policy then in effect, you must immediately stop using our Services.

If our store is acquired or merged with another company, your information may be transferred to the new owners so that we may continue to sell products to you.

**  
Section 10- Your Rights**

If you are a EU citizen or resident and would like to: access, correct, amend or delete any personal information we have about you, register a complaint, or simply want more information contact our Privacy Compliance Officer, please contact us through the contact information below.

If you’re an EU citizen or resident we note that we are processing your information in order to fulfill contracts we have with you (for example if you make an order through this site ((Pixiemarket.com)), or otherwise to pursue our legitimate business interests listed above. Please also note that you information will be transferred outside of Europe, including Canada and the United States.

California Privacy Rights -California law permits users who are California residents to request and obtain from us once a year, free of charge, a list of the Third Parties to whom we have disclosed their Personal Information (if any) for their direct marketing purposes in the prior calendar year, as well as the type of Personal Information disclosed to those parties. We do not share Personal Information with Third Parties for their own marketing purposes.

For more information about our privacy practices, questions or complaints, please contact us at hey@pixiemarket.com or by mail at

Pixie Market  
[Re: Privacy Compliance Officer]  
1117 E. Pico Blvd,  
Los Angeles, CA 90021
